[{"location":"Lesvos","subject":"location & environment","question":"Where am I?","answer":"information about the location of the city, it's distance from the main city, refugee's camps in the arrea, the exchange rate, the dominant religion, upcoming events and holidays, important words in the local launguge.","score ":1},
  {"location":"Chios","subject":"services","question":"where do you have free WiFi?","answer":"information about businesses that allow free access to their wifi, streets with free wifi network and relevant passwords when available. ","score ":2},
  {"location":"Chios","subject":"basic needs","question":"Where can I breastfeed my baby?","answer":"information about the area's cultural normas about this subject and also about designated areas where mothers can comfortably take care of their children.","score ":4},
  {"location":"Lesvos","subject":"services","question":"Where are the central transportation stations?","answer":"An explanation about the processes that need to be done before buying a travelling ticket, as well as information about the location of central transportation stations, their opening hours and travelling directions from them.","score ":3},
  {"location":"Chios","subject":"services","question":"Can I take a taxi?","answer":"provide information about the legal option for refugees to use taxi (cannot use a taxi until they are registered, nor are locals legally allowed pick up refugees in private cars). Provide this information, and information about special Designated transportation for refugees, which takes them to the registration center. ","score ":3},
  {"location":"Koln","subject":"services","question":"How do I register?","answer":"provide information about the nearest registration center and the documents needed for the process. ","score ":3},
  {"location":"Kos","subject":"legal information","question":"Why am I being fingerprinted?","answer":"Explain the meaning of the process and clarify that it does not mean that the person have to stay at the country where he / she underwent the process. ","score ":1},
  {"location":"Kos","subject":"legal information","question":"How long must I stay here before I can leave?","answer":"Information about the average waiting time until registration documents are approved and / or to mean time till the  designated transport arrive, in addition to places where you can wait comfortly.","score ":2},
  {"location":"Kos","subject":"services","question":"Where can I change money?","answer":"","score ":3},
  {"location":"Koln","subject":"services","question":"Where do I get a SIM card?","answer":"","score ":5},
  {"location":"Koln","subject":"basic needs","question":"Where can I get milk for my baby?","answer":"","score ":6},
  {"location":"Koln","subject":"legal information","question":"how can I become a asylum-seeker here?","answer":"","score ":7},
  {"location":"Koln","subject":"","question":"people around you were also intersted in….","answer":"","score ":1},
  {"location":"Koln","subject":"services","question":"where can I find a free doctor?","answer":"","score ":1},
  {"location":"Koln","subject":"basic needs","question":"where can I sleep?","answer":"","score ":1},
  {"location":"Koln","subject":"services","question":"which NGOs can help me?","answer":"","score ":1},
  {"location":"Lesvos","subject":"basic needs","question":"are there any communities I can join?","answer":"","score ":1},
  {"location":"Lesvos","subject":"","question":"where can I find global-phone service? ","answer":"","score ":1},
  {"location":"Lesvos","subject":"","question":"how do I say…","answer":"","score ":1},
  {"location":"Lesvos","subject":"","question":"where can I charge my cell-phone?","answer":"","score ":1}]